Let me go ahead and open up Logos Bible Software.
And let's begin with something very easy and something brand new.
you may have already noticed it in the Logos window right here.
And that little calendar icon
is to let you know that you have a reading plan associated with this book.
And the nice shortcut
about this is when you click on it, it goes to the next reading automatically and enables it so you
know exactly what you have to read and where you are in the process.
And of course, as you scroll
down and read the text, you also will see a Mark As Done button.
And when you click that, you can
see now it moves you to Psalm 3.
And so it'll keep track for you where your next read in that book
is.
And that's such a helpful shortcut.